## **EDER**

# **NONATO FERNANDES**

IT ANALYST

(55) 11 9.9725-4471

■ edernonato@outlook.com

São Paulo 08450-480

Eder Nonato Fernandes

<u>GitHub</u>

Brazilian, 28 years old

#### \_ \_

ABOUT

IT professional with
experience in ITIL
methodologies, IT
Infrastructure, and Systems
Implementation /
Administration.

MF

Experience in IT installation, support and troubleshooting. Zabbix, Grafana and Virtual Machines implementation and management. Mail Server administration and Inventory management. Experience and courses in Python, Java, Windows Server, AD, GPO, WSUS, DNS, FS, Linux, HelpDesk, Service Now, Firewall, PABX and Azure.

## EDUCATION

#### Information Systems

*Universidade Nove de Julho* 2020-2023

#### **Electronics Technician Course**

Escola Técnica Estadual (ETEC) 2010-2012

#### IT Courses (Udemy)

- Windows Server 2019
- Active Directory and Group Policy
- Zabbix 5 Application and Network Monitoring
- Grafana
- Kerio Control Firewall
- Azure Cloud Computing

#### IT / CPU Maintenance

Instituto Carlos Baccelar 80 hours each.

#### SKILLS

- Troubleshooting Skills
- Monitoring using Zabbix and Grafana
- EFSET English Certificate 72/100 C2
   Proficient (Listening and Reading skills)
- Proactive and detail-oriented
- Python and Java Development

## EXPERIENCE

#### Sr. Network Analyst / Team Coordinator

Telus International / Robert Half 02/2022 – 04/2022

Coordinator of the Brazilian side of an international scrum team, responsible for collecting data for AI improvements.

- Coordinate and manage the actions of the team
- Network troubleshooting
- Agile methodologies.

#### **IT Assistant**

Reis Office Products Serviços LTDA 03/2021 – 09/2021

Management and administration of Help Desk tickets, troubleshooting and improvements of the IT infrastructure. Analysis and implementation of best practices of Information Security. Utilization of ITIL methodologies in IT services and processes. Installation of ERP Analysis.

- Installation and maintenance of devices for users.
- Administration of Mail-Server, Inventory, Help Desk and Intranet.
- Research, implementation and management of the Zabbix monitoring system.

#### **Documents Production Operator**

Reis Office Products Serviços LTDA 02/2019 - 03/2021 (ABB/ ABB HITACH)

Management of the printing devices in client premises.

- Installation and maintenance of devices, drivers and management of the system (Uniflow).
- Remote access to Servers for creation and management of ports.